♪The painting is filled with old dreams and the moonlight is scattered♪
♪ اللوحة مليئة بالأحلام القديمة وضوء القمر متناثر ♪
♪I draw a flower when the light is half dim♪
♪ أرسم زهرة عندما يكون الضوء نصف خافت
♪The wind blows through the eyebrows and the insanity remains♪
تهب الرياح عبر الحاجبين ويبقى الجنون ♪
♪One more step and everything will be fine♪
♪ خطوة أخرى وسيكون كل شيء على ما يرام
♪Who says that things are unpredictable? You're still around♪
♪ من قال أن الأشياء لا يمكن التنبؤ بها؟  أنت ما زلت في الجوار ♪
♪The lonely shadows of the past have gone♪
اختفت الظلال الوحيدة للماضي
♪I'll take the hardships and turn them into liquor♪
♪ سآخذ المصاعب وأحولها إلى خمور
♪Old friends will never be forgotten♪
♪ لن يُنسى الأصدقاء القدامى
♪Who says the world has changed? You never left♪
♪ من قال أن العالم قد تغير؟  أنت لم تغادر أبدًا ♪
♪Yesterday's sorrows and joys are long gone♪
ولت منذ فترة طويلة أحزان وأفراح الأمس ♪
♪I hold the light in my hands only to see this love last♪
♪ أحمل الضوء في يدي فقط لأرى هذا الحب أخيرًا
♪A million dreams for me to look back on♪
♪ مليون حلم بالنسبة لي لأنظر إليها مرة أخرى ♪
=Order of the Sommelier= =Episode 1=
= ترتيب الساقي = = الحلقة 1 =
(Underage viewers are advised to watch under parental consent.)
(يُنصح المشاهدين القاصرين بالمشاهدة بموافقة الوالدين).
(Genius Sommelier, Fu Yu)
(جينيوس سوميلير ، فو يو)
(Famous Genius Sommelier, Fu Yu)
(الشهير جينيوس سوميلير ، فو يو)
(Why are there all my posters?)
(لماذا توجد كل ملصقاتي؟)
(Is this a bar owned by my fan?)
(هل هذه حانة مملوكة لمعجبي؟)
What a good-looking man.
يا له من رجل وسيم.
Why are you frozen? She's talking about you.
لماذا انت مجمدة  إنها تتحدث عنك.
Don't go. There's more.
لا تذهب.  هناك المزيد.
=Order of the Sommelier=
= ترتيب الساقي =
Come on. Have a drink.
تعال.  تناول مشروب.
Hi there.
أهلاً.
Boss.
رئيس.
(Bai Qi, owner of Demon Tavern)
(باي كي ، صاحب Demon Tavern)
Is your shabby bar
(Bai Qi ، مالك Demon Tavern) هو شريطك المتهالك
haunted?
(باي كي ، صاحب Demon Tavern) مسكون؟
(Bai Qi, owner of Demon Tavern)
(باي كي ، صاحب Demon Tavern)
It's your first time here.
(Bai Qi ، مالك Demon Tavern) إنها المرة الأولى لك هنا.
You haven't even had a drink
لم تشرب حتى
and you're already drunk talking.
وأنت مخمور بالفعل تتحدث.
Instead of ghosts,
بدلا من الأشباح
my place is full of drunkards.
مكاني مليء بالسكارى.
If you're freaked out
إذا كنت خائفا
by the name of my bar,
باسم الحانة الخاصة بي ،
you could use a drink.
يمكنك استخدام مشروب.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
I'll pour you
سوف أسكب لك
a double vodka.
فودكا مزدوجة.
It's on the house.
انه في المنزل.
I have had more liquor
لقد تناولت المزيد من الخمور
than you have drunk water.
مما شربته من الماء.
Hey.
يا.
Are you trying to fool me
هل تحاول خداعى
with a vodka?
مع الفودكا؟
No way.
مستحيل.
I serve beer to gentlemen
أنا أقدّم الجعة إلى السادة
for their enjoyment.
من أجل متعتهم.
I serve red liquor to those who are passionately in love
أنا أخدم الخمور الحمراء لأولئك الذين يحبونها بشغف
to make them forget about their past relationships.
لجعلهم ينسون علاقاتهم السابقة.
And for you...
ولك...
I haven't concocted
لم أقم بتلفيقها
the suitable liquor for you yet.
الخمور المناسبة لك حتى الآن.
But I've got a name for it.
لكن لدي اسم لها.
Sober Demon.
رصين شيطان.
It's the signature of my bar.
إنه توقيع البار الخاص بي.
You'll be sure to get your tastebuds back.
ستكون على يقين من استعادة براعم التذوق الخاصة بك.
So,
لذا،
(Sommelier lost his sense of taste?) you've lost your sense of taste?
(الساقي فقد حاسة التذوق؟) هل فقدت حاسة التذوق لديك؟
(Is this true or has he lost his touch?)
(هل هذا صحيح أم أنه فقد لمسته؟)
Vintners nowadays are so desperate.
الخمارون في الوقت الحاضر يائسون للغاية.
They've gone to such lengths
لقد ذهبوا إلى هذا الحد
with their marketing concepts.
بمفاهيمهم التسويقية.
Boss.
رئيس.
Were you a con man
هل كنت رجل مخادع
before you opened this bar?
قبل أن تفتح هذا الشريط؟
You keep talking about demons.
أنت تستمر في الحديث عن الشياطين.
This is a harmonious society.
هذا مجتمع متناغم.
No rumours.
لا شائعات.
No superstition.
لا خرافة.
Do you know why
هل تعرف لماذا
this place is called the Demon Tavern?
هذا المكان يسمى Demon Tavern؟
I read a book before.
قرأت كتابا من قبل.
There was a line in it
كان هناك خط فيه
that I particularly liked.
التي أحببتها بشكل خاص.
A demon
شيطان
is a creature who seeks but cannot find.
مخلوق يبحث ولا يجد.
If you don't believe me, look behind you.
إذا كنت لا تصدقني ، انظر خلفك.
Observe carefully.
راقب بعناية.
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
Welcome.
مرحباً.
This...
هذا...
This is...
هذا هو...
Am I having
هل لدي
bogus liquor?
الخمور الزائفة؟
See?
يرى؟
Am I having bogus liquor?
هل لدي خمور زائفة؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I'm talking about you.
انا أتحدث عنك.
You are making no sense.
أنت لا معنى له.
Demons?
شياطين؟
Seek but not find?
تسعى ولكن لا تجد؟
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
What kind of demon am I?
أي نوع من الشيطان أنا؟
You?
أنت؟
You are too paranoid
أنت بجنون العظمة جدا
to be a demon
لتكون شيطان
and you are too temperamental
وأنت مزاجي للغاية
to be human.
أن تكون إنسانًا.
So you are now
إذن أنت الآن
half-human and half-demon.
نصف إنسان ونصف شيطان.
In short,
باختصار،
human-demon. [*Homophone for "transgender"]
شيطان بشري.  [* Homophone for "transgender"]
Very funny.
مضحك للغاية.
Drinking is just for fun
الشرب لمجرد التسلية
and chatting.
والدردشة.
What can I get you?
ماذا يمكن أن أحضر لك؟
I heard that the owner
سمعت أن المالك
can make a drink
يمكن أن تشرب
that brings people into a dream.
التي تجلب الناس إلى حلم.
I want the kind
اريد النوع
that makes me dive into a sweet dream.
هذا يجعلني أغوص في حلم جميل.
It's not always a sweet dream.
إنه ليس دائمًا حلم جميل.
You have to be careful.
عليك أن تكون حذرا.
Don't dream of
لا تحلم
a nightmare with
كابوس مع
all those creepy demons.
كل هؤلاء الشياطين المخيفة.
That's horrifying.
هذا مرعب.
And I don't think
ولا أعتقد
it's a good idea to drink
من الجيد أن تشرب
with your eyes condition.
مع حالة عينيك.
I had poor eyesight since I was a child.
كنت أعاني من ضعف في البصر منذ أن كنت طفلاً.
The other eye is almost blind, too.
العين الأخرى تقريبًا عمياء أيضًا.
It doesn't matter to me.
لا يهمني.
But I have a friend
لكن لدي صديق
I haven't seen in 12 years.
لم أر منذ 12 عاما.
If possible,
إذا كان ذلك ممكنا،
I would like to see him in my dream.
أود أن أراه في حلمي.
Leave it to me.
اتركه لي.
Why do you take on
لماذا تأخذ على
all kinds of work?
كل أنواع العمل؟
However, you need to
ومع ذلك ، أنت بحاجة إلى
make this liquor with me.
اجعل هذا الخمور معي.
What is your impression of him?
ما هو انطباعك عنه؟
He is about my age.
هو في عمري تقريبا.
He's a very gentle person.
إنه شخص لطيف للغاية.
He would always send me
كان يرسل لي دائما
wheat breads and tea from his village.
خبز القمح والشاي من قريته.
I'm drooling just thinking about it.
أنا يسيل لعابي فقط أفكر فيه.
We are both very busy.
كلانا مشغول جدا
We haven't seen each other for years.
لم نر بعضنا البعض منذ سنوات.
I often think of him,
كثيرا ما أفكر فيه ،
but there's always
ولكن هناك دائما
something missing in the memory.
شيء مفقود في الذاكرة.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
You picked such a fine liquor.
لقد اخترت هذا النوع من الخمور الجيدة.
Rich and mellow.
غنية وناضجة.
Hey.
يا.
I picked this liquor first.
اخترت هذا الخمور أولا.
Take your hands off.
ارفع يديك.
This liquor is very fruity.
هذا الخمور فاكهي جدا.
You should not add too many
يجب ألا تضيف الكثير
additional ingredients.
مكونات إضافية.
I know what I'm doing.
أنا أعرف ما أفعله.
I sense that
أشعر بذلك
you guys are very good friends.
أنتم يا رفاق أصدقاء جيدون جدًا.
- Impossible.
- مستحيل.  - مستحيل.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Hallucinogen?
مهلوس؟
I know you lost your job after losing your sense of taste,
أعلم أنك فقدت وظيفتك بعد أن فقدت حاسة التذوق لديك ،
but don't come ruining my business,
لكن لا تأتوا لتدمير عملي ،
okay?
تمام؟
You know what?
أتعلم؟
You are so annoying.
انت مزعج جدا.
What exactly is this?
ما هذا بالضبط؟
Genius sommelier.
ساقي عبقرية.
Why don't you try it?
لماذا لا تجربها؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Too chicken to drink?
دجاجة جدا للشرب؟
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
Fine.
بخير.
Let's drink together.
لنشرب سويا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Come on.
تعال.
It's thundering.
إنها مدوية.
(I'm scared of thunder.)
(أنا خائف من الرعد).
(This is a bad omen!)
(هذا نذير شؤم!)
(No wonder the demon hunter)
(لا عجب صائد الشياطين)
(chased me all the way.)
(طاردني طوال الطريق).
(No, I have to run.)
(لا ، لا بد لي من الركض).
(You have no way to run.)
(ليس لديك طريقة للجري).
(You don't have to be so serious.)
(ليس عليك أن تكون جادًا جدًا.)
(Please.)
(لو سمحت.)
(Take it easy.)
(خذها ببساطة.)
(Don't be so serious.)
(لا تكن جادًا جدًا.)
(You run quite fast.)
(أنت تركض بسرعة كبيرة).
(I am so unlucky to meet a demon hunter)
(أنا غير محظوظ للغاية لمقابلة صائد الشياطين)
(in the middle of a thunderstorm.)
(في منتصف عاصفة رعدية.)
(I'm just saying.)
(أنا فقط أقول.)
(It doesn't really have to be this bad.)
(لا يجب أن تكون بهذا السوء حقًا.)
(What is this?)
(ما هذا؟)
(He's dead.)
(هو ميت.)
(Whatever.)
(أيا كان.)
(A villager of Hedong Village, Hu Shen)
(قروي من قرية هيدونغ ، هو شين)
(My head.)
(قروي من قرية هيدونغ ، هو شين) (رأسي).
(What has this man been through?)
(بماذا مر هذا الرجل؟)
(Hu Shen)
(هو شين)
(Hu Shen?)
(هو شين؟)
Fortunately, he just died recently.
لحسن الحظ ، توفي للتو مؤخرًا.
There is still the smell of a human body.
لا تزال هناك رائحة جسم الإنسان.
With this body,
مع هذا الجسم ،
there's nothing
لا يوجد شيء
God can do about me for now.
يمكن أن يفعل الله بي الآن.
How about me? What will I do with you?
ماذا عني؟  ماذا سأفعل بك؟
Master.
يتقن.
Why are you still chasing me?
لماذا ما زلت تطاردني؟
I'm just a little fox.
أنا مجرد ثعلب صغير.
I'm not evil.
أنا لست شريرا.
You are a demon.
انت شيطان.
All demons in this world
كل الشياطين في هذا العالم
are evil.
هم شريرون.
So they must die.
لذلك يجب أن يموتوا.
♪Which door to open so that I can see you again?♪
♪ أي باب يفتح حتى أتمكن من رؤيتك مرة أخرى؟
♪When the world is snowing heavily♪
♪ عندما يتساقط العالم بغزارة
♪I look back and you still look the same♪
♪ أنظر إلى الوراء وما زلت تبدو كما لو كنت
♪I lost my friends and started to wander♪
♪ فقدت أصدقائي وبدأت أتجول ♪
♪Which liquor shall I drink with you?♪
أي خمور أشرب معك؟
♪We'll drink and travel to a certain place♪
سنشرب ونسافر إلى مكان معين
♪The world and the spiritual realm are all connected♪
العالم والعالم الروحي مترابطان جميعًا ♪
♪Remembering the old days♪
تذكر الأيام الخوالي ♪
♪The past is quietly waiting to be unsealed♪
الماضي ينتظر بهدوء أن يُفتح ♪
♪It reminds me of my intent♪
يذكرني بنيتي ♪
♪Why is reality sometimes more like a dream than memories♪
♪ لماذا يكون الواقع أحيانًا أشبه بالحلم أكثر من الذكريات ♪
♪We promised to walk together through the glory♪
وعدنا أن نسير معًا في المجد
♪I once had you to see the whole world together♪
♪ لقد جعلتك ذات مرة ترى العالم كله معًا
(Do not sell alcohol to minors. Underage drinking is not permitted.)
(لا تبيع الكحول للقصر. لا يُسمح بتناول المشروبات الكحولية دون السن القانونية).